A Guide to The Papers of Robert C. Fitzgerald, 1973-1988
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
The Papers of Robert C. Fitzgerald 1973-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
MSS 04-4
Twenty three boxes
The papers of Robert C. Fitzgerald consist primarily of professional papers regarding issues of annexation in the State of Virginia.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was donated to the Law School Special Collections Department in June of 2004.
Biographical Information
Robert Clayton Fitzgerald was born September 22, 1921. He was a graduate of George Washington High School in Alexandria, Va. He received his B.A. from the University of Virginia in 1941 and his J.D., also from the University of Virginia, in 1946. From 1942 to 1945 he served in the Marine Corps as a 2nd Lieutenant and fought on the Pacific front. In 1946 Mr. Fitzgerald began practicing law in Falls Church, Va. He was appointed judge of Trail Justice and Juvenile and Domestic Relations Courts in Fairfax, Va. in 1951, where he served until 1954 when he was appointed Commonwealth's attorney of Fairfax County, a position he held until 1963 when he was elected to the Virginia Senate representing the counties of Fairfax and Arlington and the cities of Falls Church and Fairfax. Mr. Fitzgerald served as Chairman of the Virginia Airports Authority, The Dulles Airport Commission, and the Virginia Advisory Legislative Council; he was member of the Senate Ethics Committee and he served as president of The George Mason University Foundation.
From 1965 to 1993 he was head of the law firm Fitzgerald and Smith of Fairfax, Va. In 1993 he accepted an appointment of counsel to the law firm of Hazel and Thomas. Mr. Fitzgerald retired in 1999.
Mr. Fitzgerald's other activities included serving as president of the Fairfax County Bar and the Commonwealth's Attorneys Association. He was dean of the Delta Theta Legal Fraternity, he was a deacon in the Middleburg Baptist Church and a member of the Staunton Baptist Church in Huddleston, Va.
Robert C. Fitzgerald died October 10, 2001 in Huddleston, Va.
Scope and Content
The Papers of Robert Clayton Fitzgerald were donated to the University of Virginia Arthur J. Morris Law Library by his wife Nancy R. Fitzgerald in June of 2004. They consist of 23 boxes, 7.7 linear feet.
The papers (1973 - 1988) pertain to Mr. Fitzgerald's practice as an attorney counseling counties and cities in the State of Virginia on issues of annexation and inter governmental affairs. The most important and complete file is Pittsylvania County - City of Danville, a case that dealt with the annexation petition of Danville, Va., and the negotiations between the city of Danville and the county of Pittsylvania in which Mr. Fitzgerald served as legal counsel for the county's Board of Supervisors.
Other files in the collection include: Albemarle County annexation in which Mr. Fitzgerald represented the county in its negotiations concerning immunity and revenue sharing with the city of Charlottesville; Fairfax City and County documents referring to city/county contracts and services (Fire Services Agreements) and questions about annexation immunity, annexation petitions, etc. James City County files where Mr. Fitzgerald was a consultant and later represented James City County officials in their negotiations with the Cities of Williamsburg and Newport News, reviewing and analyzing school contracts, water resources, annexation and consolidation proceedings. The Prince William County case in which the Law Offices of Fitzgerald & Smith supervised the study and analysis of the fiscal impact on the County of Prince William transition to city status. Mr. Fitzgerald counseled Spotsylvania County in matters of "intergovernmental concerns with other governmental institutions and intragovernmental (sic) matters".
The Fauquier County Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works Inc. is another example of Mr. Fitzgerald's practice. This case refers to the condemnation proceedings pursuant to title 25, chapter 1.1 of the Code of Virginia of the Marshall Water Works and the interest of Fauquier County and Water Authority to purchase the company.
The Family Savings and Loan of Virginia of Springfield, Virginia documents principally relate to the mergers of the company with Virginia First Savings and Loan Association of Petersburg, Va., and other similar financial institutions. Mr. Fitzgerald was chairman of the Board of Family Savings and Loan of Virginia and Subsidiaries.
There is also some personal and professional correspondence (1979), trustees files (1977-1979) and some financial statements of Family Savings and Loan (1980-1983.
Arrangement
These papers were arranged in three parts:
Part 1: Personal and Professional Correspondence, and Trustees Files.
Part 2: Annexation Cases organized in alphabetical order, and chronological order within the case.
Part 3: Family Savings and Loan of Virginia and Fauquier County Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works Inc. Files
Contents List
- Personal and Professional Correspondence, Trustees Files
  - Fitzgerald, Robert C. Personal Correspondence 1979 (Box 1)
  - Fitzgerald, Robert C. Professional Outgoing Correspondence 1979 (Box 1)
    (2 folders)
  - Fitzgerald, Robert C. Trustees Files (Released deeds, etc.) 1977-1979 (Box 1)
  - Fiztgerald and Smith, P. C. - Family Savings and Loan [Financial] Statements 1980, Feb. - Jan. 1983 (Box 1)
- Annexation Cases
  - Annexation - General. Miscellaneous copies of documents re annexation in the state of Virginia 1964-1975 (Box 2)
    (3 folders)
  - Annexation - General. Newspaper clippings 1980-1982, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Albemarle County - Annexation. Albemarle County Code. Subdivision of Land n.d. (ca. 1980) (Box 2)
  - Albemarle County - Annexation. City of Charlottesville Proposal and Statement; Preliminary Report to the Board of Supervisors of Albemarle County by Legal Counsel 1980 (Box 2)
  - Albemarle County - Annexation. Correspondence between George St. John, county attorney and Fiztgerald 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - Albemarle County - Annexation. Newspaper clippings 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - Fairfax City Miscellaneous Documents: Available funds from revenue sharing; Krasnow v. City and County of Fairfax Bill of Complaint; Northern Virginia Police Academy Lease; Adult Detention Facilities 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Fairfax City and County - Fire Services Agreements and Recommended Agenda for Renegotiating Fairfax City contracts; Correspondence 1974-1978 (Box 3)
  - Fairfax County - Fitzgerald and Smith Financial Statements 1975-1979 (Box 3)
  - Fairfax County - Annexation. Immunity 1976-1982 (Box 3)
  - Fairfax City/County - Negotiations. Correspondence re City/County Contracts and Services 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Fairfax County/City - Negotiations. Correspondence between Fitzgerald and Smith and County; memoranda, reports, miscellaneous documents. 1977-1978 (Box 4)
    (4 folders)
  - Fairfax City/County - Negotiations of contracts with City of Fairfax. 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Fairfax County - Schools. Miscellaneous documents 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Fairfax County - Schools. Tuition contracts 1975-1977 (Box 5)
  - Fairfax County - Reston. [Proposed Charter for Town of Reston] 1973-1980 (Box 6)
  - Fairfax County - Sewer System. Sewer cases (Box 6)
  - Fairfax County - Sewer System. Disburment of checks. 1980 (Box 6)
  - James City County - General. Contracts, court order, newspaper clippings. 1955-1978 (Box 7)
  - James City County - Correspondence re annexation 1976-1981 (Box 7)
  - James City County Maps: Existing Utilities, Rate Study, Water and Sewer Facilities Map, Base Map prepared by Wiley & Wilson, Inc. Additional data Obtained from City of Williamsburg, James City County, City of Williamsburg and Environs. n.d., 1978-1979 (Box Oversize Shelf)
  - James City County - Water resources research, printed cases and authorities; handwritten notes 1978 (Box 7)
  - James City County - Memoranda, reports of annexation meetings, maps 1978-1980 (Box 7)
  - James City County - Data. [Public Facilities Plan; Analysis of the James City County-Williamsburg Joint School System; Population information, Assessment information; Capital Improvements Budget Information, Service Authority]. [Maps of Existing Facilities in James City County, BAse Map of Williamsburg, James City Council and Map of City of Williamsburg and Environs] 1979 (Box 8 and Oversize Shelves)
  - James City County - Data list; Resolution and Contract for the Joint Operation of Schools with the City of Williamsburg; Commission on Local Government Rules of Procedure 1980 (Box 8)
  - Loundon County Annexation. [Proposition, agreements, etc.] 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville - Annexation. Prior annexation data; Hesse Hodnett, et al v. City of Danville; cross examinations and exhibits. 1975, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Pittsylvania County Memorandum to Board of Supervisors re proposed annexation by the city of Danville 1976, Aug. 30 (Box 9)
  - Pittsylvania County Annexation - Correspondence 1982, Apr. 19 - Jul. 19, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Pittsylvania County Annexation - City, County, Service Authority Agreements 1982, Dec. 8 [1972-1982] (Box 9)
  - Pittsylvania County Annexation - City of Danville. Correspondence with Commission on Local Government 1983, Mar. - Feb. 1984 (Box 9)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville - Injunction Correspondence 1983, Mar. - Jun. (Box 9)
  - Pittsylvania County - Annexation. City of Danville Interrogatories and Production of Documents to County 1983, Apr. - May (Box 9)
  - City of Danville Attachments to County Answers to City Interrogatories 1983, May (1978-1983) (Box 10)
  - City of Danville. Commission on Local Government Interrogatory to County of Pittsylvania [to assist in the review of the annexation and immunity issues] 1983, Jul. - Ago. (Box 10)
  - Pittsylvania County Planning Commission. School Appraisal Data. 1983, Aug. (Box 10)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville. Correspondence. Three Judge Court 1983, Sep. - Oct. (Box 10)
  - Pittsylvania County - Annexation Witness Testimony. [Evaluations, questions, notes, lists]. 1983, Oct. 24 (Box 10)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County and Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville re: Annexation and Petition of Partial Immunity. Hearings. 1983, Nov. 1 (Box 10)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville. City's Response to Question 13 1983, Dec. 8 (Box 11)
  - Pittsylvania County - Annexation Newspaper Clippings 1983 (Box 11)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Immunity Court Orders. 1983-1985 (Box 11)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville re Extension of Time for Filing Report by Commission on Local Government. Motions. 1984, Jan. 11 (Box 11)
  - Pittsylvania County Partial Immunity Notice Revised from May 1984 1984, May (Box 11)
  - City of Danville v. County of Pittsylvania - Annexation. Correspondence 1984, Jul. - Dec. 1987 (Box 11)
  - Pittsylvania County re: Value of Pittsylvania County Service Authority 1984, Jul. - Feb. 1985 (Box 11)
  - Pittsylvania County Immunity Suit Appeal. Correspondence. 1984, Jul. - Aug. 1985 (Box 11)
  - County of Pittsylvania v. City of Danville - Annexation Financial Exhibits. 1984, Jul. - Dec. 1985 (Box 12)
  - County of Pittsylvania v. City of Danville Findings of Fact and Conclusion of Law 1984, Sep. - Nov. (Box 12)
  - Board of Supervisors of the County of Pittsylvania v. City of Danville. Immunity Pleadings 1984, Sep. (Box 12)
  - Board of Supervisors of the County of Pittsylvania v. City of Danville Immunity [Commission on Local Government Report: Augusta County] 1984, Sep. (Box 12)
  - Board of Supervisors of the County of Pittsylvania v. City of Danville. Exception to the Report of the Commission on Local Government 1984, Nov.29 (Box 12)
  - Pittsylvania County Immunity. Clarence Edmunds, Andrew Berky and Claude Whitehead Outlines of Testimony n.d. (Box 12)
  - Pittsylvania County Immunity. Garland Page Outline of Testimony n.d. (Box 12)
  - Pittsylvania County Immunity Suit Appeal. Goodyear Agreement 1985 (Box 12)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County - Annexation. City Compromise and County Response 1985, Feb. (Box 12)
  - Pittsylvania County Immunity Suit Appeal. [Final draft of Memorandum of Pittsylvania County on Legal Standards for Granting Partial Immunity; Petition for Appeal]. 1985, May (Box 12)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County - Annexation. Exhibits. 1985, May - Oct. (Box 12)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Immunity Appeal Pleadings 1985, May; Feb. 1986 (Box 12)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County, et al. County Production of Documents to the City 1985, Jun. - Oct. (Box 12)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County - Annexation. Memorandum of Pittsylvania County in Support of Pleas in Bar and to the Jurisdiction. 1985, Jun. 25 (Box 12)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County - Annexation. Answer by City of Danville Petition to Intervene by USG Industries, Inc. 1985, Jul. 15 (Box 12)
  - Pittsylvania County - Annexation. City of Danville Writ of Prohibition 1985, Aug. - Sep. (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County Audit Letter 1985, Sep. 19 and 27 (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County - Annexation - Loss of Net Tax Revenue. 1985, Sep. - Nov. (Box 13)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County - Annexation. Intervenor Post Trial Pleadings 1985, Oct. 22 - Nov. 6; 1986, May (Box 13)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County, et al - Annexation. Response by Danville to Interrogatories and Motion to Extend Discovery. 1985, Nov. 29. (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Immunity Appeal Correspondence 1985, Dec. 15 - Jan. (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Immunity Appeal Work File. [Brief of Appellant; Brief in Opposition to Petition for Appeal; Reply Brief of Appellant; Brief of Appellee]. 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Petition for Appeal re Opinion of the Court in Danville Annexation Case. [ca. 1986] (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville - Annexation. Opinion of the Court. 1986; Feb. 12 (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County - Annexation. Pittsylvania County - City of Danville Negotiations. 1986, Jul. 7-11 (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville - Annexation Appeal, Pleadings 1986, Jul. (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville - Annexation Appeal Correspondence. 1986, Jul. - Nov. (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville - Annexation Appeal Pleadings. 1986, Jul. (Box 13)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Petition for Appeal and Petition for Appeal Appendixes 1986, Oct. (Box 14)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County - Annexation Debt Schedule 1987, Mar. 30 (Box 14)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County - Annexation. Joint Motion to Modify Order. 1987, Mar. 30 (Box 14)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County Settlement Order. 1987, Apr. 20; Dec. 1988 (Box 14)
  - City of Danville v. Pittsylvania County - Annexation Water and Sewer Agreements. 1983; 1987 (Box 14)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Steps for Approval of Agreement n.d. (Box 14)
  - Pittsylvania County - Annexation [Miscellaneous documents]. Report on the County of Augusta Partial Immunity Action and Report on the Immunity and Financial Settlement Provisions of the City of Staunton - County of Augusta Settlement Agreement. 1982, Dec.; 1985, Sep. (Box 14)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit. County Request for Production of Documents No. 2. [City Utility Rates: electricity, street lights, water and wastewater, gas; sewer connections ordinances]. 1979-1983 (Box 14)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville License Tax Suit Research and Data; Wingate Reappraisal, General Highway Map of Pittsylvania County. 1982-1987 (Box 14)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit Research 1982, Dec. 14 (Box 14)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit. Bill in Equity 1983, Feb. - Sep. (Box 14)
  - [Maps of City of Danville and Pittsylvania County]: General pertinent data. Study Area A and B; Map of Danville and Pittsylvania Co. n.d., ca. 1983 (Box Oversize Shelves)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit - Memoranda, Pleadings 1983, Mar. 8 - May 8, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit - Pleadings 1983, Mar. - Jun. (Box 15)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit - Correspondence 1983, Jun. - Dec. (Box 15)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit - City Answer to County Interrogatories No. 2, No. 7, No. 15. 1983, Sep. (Box 15)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit - City Response to County Request for Production of Documents. (Chancery No. 13). 1983, Sep. 28 (Box 15)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit (Chancery 13) - Request for Admissions; Second Request for Admissions 1984, Apr. (Box 15)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit. Proposed Final Decree, Findings of Fact. 1984, Jul. - Nov. (Box 15)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Tax Suit - Pittsylvania County Board of Supervisors Annexation Negotiation Team Meeting. 1984, Aug. 3 (Box 15)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville License Tax - Correspondence 1984, Dec. - Nov. 1988 (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville Utility Franchise Tax 1985, May 1 (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville License Tax - Discovery 1985, Jul. - Sep. (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville License Tax - Orders 1985-1986 (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville License Tax - Joint Stipulations (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County v. city of Danville License Tax - Pleadings 1985-1987 (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville License Tax - Interrogatories to City. 1987 (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County v. City of Danville License Tax - Argument on behalf of Pittsylvania County upon Evidence; Reply Memorandum by the City of Danville in Support of Demurrer and Answer; Final Decree 1987, Apr. - Jun. (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County and Pittsylvania County Service Authority v. City of Danville Injunction Suit. Bill for Injunction Relief, Memoranda to Support Motions. 1983 (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County and Pittsylvania County Service Authority v. City of Danville - County Injunction; Suit for Injunction Pleadings. 1983, Jun. - Aug. (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County and Pittsylvania County Service Authority v. City of Danville - Petition for Temporary Injunction Under Section 8.21-626. Accompanied by copies of Proceedings and Original Papers and Court Order. 1983, Aug. - Oct. (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County and Pittsylvania County Service Authority v. City of Danville - County Injunction Discovery 1983, Jul. - Sep. (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County and Pittsylvania County Service Authority v. City of Danville - County Injunction Memoranda. City, County and Commission on Local Government 1983, Jul. Sep. (Box 16)
  - Pittsylvania County and Pittsylvania and PCSA [Petitioners of Pittsylvania County Service Authority] v. City of Danville - Petition for Appeal. (Box 16)
  - Prince William County - City Status. The Fiscal Capacity of Prince William County to Function as a City and Provide Appropriate Services. Report to the Board of Supervisors of Prince William County [1981] (Box 17)
  - Prince William County - City Status Miscellaneous Documents [Agreements, reports, maps] 1981 (Box 17)
  - Prince William County - Status of Water and Sewer Utilities Proposal by Camp, Dresse & McKee 1981 (Box 17)
  - Prince William County - City. Scope of Work 1981, Sep. (Box 17)
  - Prince William County - City Status Correspondence 1981, Sep. - May 1982 (Box 17)
  - Prince William County - City Status. Newspaper Clippings 1981, Dec. - Feb. 1982 (Box 17)
  - Prince William County - Petition for Immunity 1982, Feb. - Mar. (Box 17)
  - Spotsylvania County - City of Fredericksburg Agreement by and among City of Fredericksburg, Board of Supervisors of Stafford County and Rappahanock Service Authority. Memorandum to City Desk. 1976, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Spotsylvania County - Annexation. Correspondence. 1978, Jul. - Nov. 1981 (Box 17)
  - Spotsylvania County - Billing. 1979, Sep. - Jul. 1981 (Box 17)
  - Spotsylvania County Purchase of FMC [Corporation} Facility 1980 (Box 18)
  - Spotsylvania County Miscellaneous Documents: contracts, utility system appraisal, reports, agreement. 1980-1982 (Box 18)
  - Spotsylvania County - Gardner, Cranwell & Rocovich Submittal. [Re: in the matter of Spotsylvania County Claim of Partial Immunity from City-Initiates Annexation and Incorporation of New Cities, Pursuant to Title 15.1, Chapter 19.1 and 21.2 of the Virginia COde and Part III of the Rules of Procedure of the COmmission on Local Government. Spotsylvania County v. City of Fredericksburg. Notice Pursuant to Title 15.1, Chapter 19.1 of the Virginia Code. Anno. Map.] 1981, Sep. (Box 18)
  - Spotsylvania County - Annexation. Newspaper Clippings 1979-1982 (Box 18)
  - Spotsylvania County Miscellaneous Maps: Rappahanock Valley - Fredericksburg, RADCO Planning District 16; Spotsylvania County Public Facilities; Spotsylvania County Existing Zoning Districts; Proposed Land Use, Primary Settlement Area; Spotsylvania County Recreational Facilities/Sites; Spotsylvania County General Highway Map Supplement A; Spotsylvania County General Highway map; City of Fredericksburg and Environs Base Map prepared by Wiley & Wilson Architects-Engineers-Planners. 1973-1981 (Box 18)
  - Spotsylvania County School Census. [City of Fredericksburg v. County of Spotsylvania Annexation Suit. School Membership compared to School Census. By School and Grade]. n.d. (Box 18)
  - Spotsylvania County Annexation Preliminary Exhibits. [1981] (Box 19)
  - Spotsylvania County Annexation Original Unedited Exhibits 1981 (Box 19)
  - Spotsylvania County v. City of Fredericksburg Annexation Suit. Financial Claim Exhibits. 1982, Mar. (Box 19)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke. Town of Berryville Amended Wastewater Facilities Plan EPA Project C510548-01; Commission on Local Government, Commonwealth of Virginia Rules of Procedure; Fiscal Impact of Proposed Development on the Clevenger Property; COnstruction Specifications for Berryville: Projects I and II. 1983-1987 (Box 19)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke Miscellaneous Documents re Annexation Agreement 1986-1988 (Box 19)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke. Berryville Area Master Plan. Chapter XII. Fiscal Impact Study [ca. 1987-1988] (Box 20)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke. Area Master Plan [Work Files] 1987-1988 (Box 20)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke. Constructions Specifications; Sanitary Sewer Rehabilitation; "The Orchards of Berryville": Fiscal Impacts of a 450 Unit-Single-Family Planned Unit Development of the Town of Berryville, the County of Clarke and Downtown Businesses; Impact Study of Echols Property Pud on Town of Berryville's Sewer, Water and Stormwater Facilities; Berryville Area Master Plan. 1987-1988 (Box 20)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke - Research, Contracts, Announcements, Maps. See oversize map. 1987-1989 (Box 20)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke - Town COuncil [Meeting Agendas] 1988 (Box 20)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke. Location Evaluation for First Choice Supplement North Buckmarsh St. (U. S. 340 and S. H. 7 By-Pass; "The Orchards": Fiscal Impacts for the Town, County and Downtown Businesses. 1988, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke. Newspaper Clippings. 1988-1989 (Box 21)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke Resolutions. 1988-1989 (Box 21)
  - Town of Berryville, County of Clarke - Ketoct Land Co. v. County of Clarke 1989 (Box 21)